He apparently only kills murderers.
こいつ 殺人犯しか殺さないらしいよ
I heard.
Lunatic is likely to continue doing this
えぇ
おそらく彼は犯罪者を根絶するまで
同様の事件を起こすでしょう
until every criminal is exterminated.
With Lunatic around, I don't think there'll be any crimes.
ルナティックがいたら
犯罪とか起きないんじゃね？
He's definitely stronger than the Heroes.
絶対ヒーローより強いでしょ こいつ
His face is scary.
顔 コ〜ワッ！
gokigen yo doukashitan darou?
How are you? Is something wrong?
ごきげんよう　どうかしたんだろ？
kao wo mireba isshun de wakaru yo
I can tell just by looking at you.
顔を見れば一瞬でわかるよ
senrigan senrigan? messou nai desu
Am I psychic? Of course not.
千里眼千里眼？
めっそうないです
taikutsu GIRL megumaretai no kai
Bored girl, do you want to find happiness?
退屈ガール　恵まれたいのかい
hantei wa shingi no renzoku de
Let's think it through and decide.
判定は審議の連続で
VENUS SUSTAIN
Venus Sustain.
ヴィーナスサステイン
odoru machinami
The city dances.
踊る街並み
PERFECTLY EUPHORIA
Perfectly, Euphoria!
Perfectly Euphoria！
nandemo nai youna kotoba de naitari suru shi
I end up crying over the smallest things.
何でもないような
言葉で泣いたりするし
hora bokutachi nante
Come on, our
ほら 僕たちなんて
zentei no nai
temporary passion
juubun tekido ni
lives are
十分適度に
zentei no nai
a temporary passion
DRAMATIC sa
reasonably dramatic.
ドラマチックさ
saikou no wa
the best passion
karuku SUPER STAR
We're almost like super stars!
軽くスーパースター
ORION wo nazoru konna fukai yoru
Looking up at Orion late at night.
オリオンをなぞる こんな深い夜
tsunagaretai hanasaretai
I want to connect. I want to be free.
つながりたい 離されたい
tsumari hanshinhangi acchi kocchi
Basically, I'm not sure and can't decide.
つまり半信半疑あっちこっち
shin mirai wo negau kuuzenzetsugo no
I pray for a new future. The greatest one yet.
新未来を願う 空前絶後の
kotoba ga moshi, moshi tsumugeru nara jikan ga tomaru yo
If I could spin words, time would stop.
言葉がもし もし紡げるなら
時間が止まるよ
koko de owaru hazu ga nai no ni
"There's no way it can end here."
｢ココデオワルハズガナイノニ｣
うぅ 困ったことになった
This is problematic.
I never expected this to cause people to distrust Heroes.
まさかヒーローの信頼まで
おびやかされる事になろうとは
If more people begin to question their existence...
このまま彼らの存在に
疑問の声が高まれば
ヒーローＴＶの存続も危ういですぞ
HERO TV will also be in jeopardy.
We must do everything we can to keep that from happening!
それだけは
なんとしても阻止しなければならん
彼らにどれだけ金をかけてきたか
We've poured too much money into them.
皆さん
Gentlemen.
Our current topic is Lunatic.
今の議題は ルナティックについてです
He may think he's fixing the world, but the Justic Bureau
奴は世直しでもしている
つもりなのかも しれませんが
doesn't approve of the use of capital punishment.
当局は死刑制度を認めていません
I think we should put together a plan to arrest him
これ以上 被害が広がる前に
早急に逮捕策を講じるべきだと
as soon as possible before there are any more victims.
But we don't know when he'll appear,
しかし
いつ現れるのかも わからないんじゃ
手の打ちようもないだろう
so there's nothing we can do.
そうだそうだ
That's right!
Please calm down!
落ち着いてください
The problem is that people are beginning
問題はルナティックの思想に
市民が同調し始めたことです
to support Lunatic's ideas.
Our top priority should be
ここは正義の使者が誰であるかを
明確にするため
to think of a way to regain the people's trust in Heroes
ヒーローの信頼回復を はかることが
最重要事項ではないでしょうか
and show them who the true representatives of justice are.
本日 我がヒーローアカデミーに
現役のヒーローが来てくださいました
Today, some currently active Heroes
have come to the Hero Academy.
あ〜 帰りたい
I want to go home.
あ？
Huh?
こんな暇があるなら
ルナティックを追跡すべきですよ
If we have this much free time, we should be looking for Lunatic.
Yeah,
まぁな
でも まずは信頼回復なんだと
but the higher-ups want us to regain the people's trust first.
And that's supposed to achieve our goal?
あれで回復できるんですかね？
ん？
ここで会ったが100年目
Ah, so we finally meet!
Now, I shall teach you the secret to becoming a Hero!
拙者がヒーローの真髄を
伝授するでござるよ シュッシュ
Shu, shu!
Oh man...
あちゃ〜
Okay... Everyone together! Shu, shu!
はい　皆さんもご一緒に
シュッシュ
チッ！
ふぅ　あちぃ〜
Hot...
あ〜 帰りたい
I want to go home.
まだ言ってんのかよ
You're still saying that?
あ〜 帰りたい
I want to go home.
What, you too?!
えっ　お前も？
Yeah.
うん
What happened?
どうしたんだよ？ さっきまで
Just a moment ago you were all excited
シュッシュっとかやってただろう
doing that ninja star thingie.
I was forcing myself there!
あれは無理にテンション上げただけです
本当は生徒を教える自信なんて…
I'm not really fit to teach students.
は？
Huh?
だって僕 いつも見切れてるだけだし
I mean, all I ever do is stay in the background.
And I'm the lowest-ranking Hero.
ランキングも最下位だし
And all I do is stay in the background.
見切れてるだけだし
Don't worry about that.
んなこと気にすんなよ
I also got bashed on my blog recently!
最近僕のブログも炎上したんです
Say what?
炎上？
It was full of comments telling me that
“お前はヒーローに向いてない”とか
“やめちまえ”とか
I wasn't made to be a Hero, and that I should quit.
そういうコメントばっかりで
I see. I didn't know you had a blog.
そうなんだ…
てかブログやってたんだ
I bet I'm the one most responsible for bringing down
きっとヒーローの信頼を
一番落としてるのは僕なんですよ
our reputation as Heroes.
Were you always this negative?
ねえ
君ってこんなネガティブだったの？
そろそろ いいですかな
Are you ready?
Principal Massini. It's been a long time, sir!
お久しぶりです 校長先生
Ah, Barnaby!
お〜 バーナビー！
You've become such a fine Hero.
すっかり頼もしい
ヒーローになってしまって
ここで学んだお陰です
It's all thanks to the teachings of this school.
I'm happy to hear that.
そう言ってくれると嬉しいよ
Ivan! I've been following your activities too!
イワン！　君の活躍も見とるよ
あ… 本名はやめてください
Please don't call me by my real name, sir.
いかんいかん
Ah yes! Right now I should be calling you Origami Cyclone.
今は“折紙サイクロン”と呼ばんとな
You've both become so wonderful!
しかし２人とも立派になったな
ああ！　タイガーさん
Ah! Mr. Tiger!
Pleased to meet you.
初めまして
どうも どうも すいませんね
卒業生じゃないのが１人交じっちゃって
Hello. Sorry I'm here even though I'm not a graduate.
Not at all! I'm sure the students
いいえ！　“元”人気ヒーローの登場に
生徒は喜ぶでしょう
would love to see the appearance of an ex-star Hero!
Leave out the first part,
先生“元”はいらないですよ
“人気ヒーロー”でお願いします
and just introduce me as a star Hero, okay?
さあ　皆さん
All right then.
We're all looking forward to the special lectures by you Heroes!
ヒーローならではの特別講義
期待してますよ
はいはい
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir.
Uh... yes.
あ… はい
ヒーローにとって一番重要なのは
The most important thing a Hero needs to do is to earn points.
ポイントを取ること
“取られる前に取れ”
業界では有名な言葉です
"Take it before it is taken."
It's a well-known phrase used in this industry.
はい
Yes, sir!
The most important thing a Hero needs to do
ヒーローにとって一番重要なのは
市民を守ることだ
is to protect the people!
Destroy buildings if you have to!
そのためには ビルを壊したっていい
賠償金なんか気にすんな
Don't worry about paying damage fines!
はい
Yes, sir!
The most important thing a Hero needs to do
ヒーローにとって一番重要なのは
企業へのアピールだ
is to appeal to his sponsors!
When you're on camera, make sure your logos are visible!
カメラに見切れるときは
ロゴを目立たせるでござるよ
Got that?
わかったか！
あれ？
Huh?
I'm not aiming to be on camera.
見切れるとか 目指してないし
Can you give us any tips on how to save people instead?
そんなことより人を助ける
コツを教えてもらえませんか？
えっ…
Huh?
Well...
えっと…
先生！
Mr. Tiger! Please watch me!
僕も
私も
Me too!
Mr. Tiger! Please see mine too! I'm over here!
先生！
僕も見てください こっちこっち
All right, all right. Now show me your powers!
わかったわかった じゃ能力見せてみろ
Yes, sir! This is my power.
はい 僕の能力はこれです
はぁぁ〜 ハッ！
I-Is that it?
え？そっ それだけか？
こんなに皮膚を伸ばせるんです
I can stretch my skin this far.
You've got a great smile.
笑顔はいいぞ
Mr. Tiger, I can sweat a lot.
先生　私は汗をすごく流せます
Sweat?
あ… せ？
はぁぁ〜
う〜〜ん
どうですか？
How was that?
You've got a great smile.
いい笑顔だ
僕も見てください
Watch my powers too!
私も
Me too!
And me!
はぁぁ〜
ハッ！
うぅぅ〜
ハ〜ッ！
うぅ〜 はぁ〜
ハッ！
僕たちヒーローになれますか？
Can we become Heroes?
Y-You all have great smiles, that's for sure!
みんな笑顔は合格だ
Yeah! Thank you very much.
Can I really become a Hero?
僕 ヒーローになれんのかな？
やっぱり僕じゃ無理っぽくない？
I don't think it's possible for me.
そんなことねーって
That's not true!
エドワードはいいよ
You're lucky, Edward.
Everyone says that you're bound
卒業したらヒーロー間違いなしって
言われてるじゃん
to be a Hero once you graduate.
でも僕は… 落ちこぼれだから
But I'm a failure.
おい！　諦めんのかよ？
Hey, are you going to give up?
だって僕はエドワードみたいに
ヒーロー向きの能力でもないし
My power isn't useful for being a Hero like yours is.
大丈夫だよ
お前にしかできない事があるって
You'll be fine! There's got to be something that only you can do.
僕にしかできないこと？
Something only I can do?
絶対 俺ら２人ヒーローになろうぜ
Let's make sure we both become Heroes, okay?
うん
Okay.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
おう！
Yeah!
It might be tough for them to become Heroes
あいつらの能力じゃ
ヒーローは厳しいだろうな
with those kind of powers.
They're more like circus attractions than NEXT.
ＮＥＸＴっていうかびっくり人間だよ
タイガーさん
Mr. Tiger!
おお どうした？
What's wrong?
Mind taking a look at my powers too?
僕の能力も見てもらえますか？
は？
What?
Wow!
おお すっげぇ
Amazing!
Wow! Amazing!
あ いやいや 真似しなくていいだろう
No, you don't need to copy me.
いやいや 真似しなくていいだろう
No, I'm serious.
あ　いや マジでマジで
いや マジでマジで
No, I'm serious.
いい加減にしろよ 折紙！
Cut it out, Origami!
Oh, sorry.
あ… ごめんなさい
That's an amazing power.
しかし すっげぇ 能力だよ
お前人間にも化けれるんだな
You can shape-shift into other people.
But it's not really useful in saving people.
でもこれ… 人助けには使いようなくて
You think so?
そうか？
俺に化けて ハンドレッドパワー使えばさ
You could shape-shift into me and use my Hundred Power.
I can copy a person's looks, but I can't copy their powers.
見た目はコピーできても
能力までコピーできないんです
Well, that sucks.
残念
I knew it. I'm not fit to be a Hero with a power like this.
やっぱり… こんな能力の僕は
ヒーローに向いてないんですよ
I should quit being a Hero.
僕なんてヒーローをやめるべきなんだ
うっ うわぁ
なんか俺が辛くなってきた
その顔で嘆くのやめてくれる？
Now I'm starting to feel depressed.
Can you not look like me when you're crying?
あぁ すみません
Oh, sorry!
Don't think so hard about it.
そんなに悩むことは ねえだろう
え？
Huh?
I'm sure there's something only your power
折紙の能力にしかできねえ事も
あるんじゃねぇの？
is capable of dealing with.
昔 同じこと言われました
Someone once told me the same thing.
ん？
But that friend was a NEXT who was at the top of our class.
でもその友達は
学年一のＮＥＸＴだったから
その言葉… 本気にできなくて
So I couldn't take his words seriously.
But he never became a Hero, right?
けど そいつはヒーローに
なれなかったんだろ？
で お前がなってるって事は
The fact that you became one
折紙のほうがヒーローに
向いてたってことだよ
means that you were better suited to become a Hero.
違いますよ
That's not true.
いや そういうことだろ！
Of course, it is!
You really are mistaken.
本当に違うんです！
Don't be so modest!
謙遜すんな
I told you, you're mistaken!
違うって言ってるでしょ！
He should have been the Hero, not me.
彼がヒーローになるべきだったんです
ん？
いやぁ 君が学生の頃は
何をやらせても素晴らしかった
Everything you did was perfect back when you were a student.
Why, the whole school looked up to you.
なにせ 全校生徒が
憧れていたぐらいだからね
いえ
Not really.
君のファンクラブまであったもんな
You even had a fan club. They all wore glasses just like you.
全員で君と同じメガネかけたりして
Please, you're embarrassing me.
恥ずかしいから やめてください
Oh, I'm sorry.
すまんすまん
Say... What was he like back then?
あの… どんな生徒だったんですか？
もう… いいですから
Enough already.
いや〜 バニーじゃなくて折紙のこと
Not you, Bunny. I'm talking about Origami.
あ…
ああ イワン君はね　おとなしい子でしたよ
Oh... Well, Ivan...
He was very quiet...
always hiding behind his closest friend at the academy.
仲のいい生徒がいまして
その子の陰にいつも隠れてました
それって
学年一のＮＥＸＴだったっていう
Is that the NEXT who was at the top of his class?
Yes. He was a very gifted student.
ええ とても優秀な生徒でした
But he caused an incident as a student here.
しかし在学中にある事件を起こしまして
事件？
An incident?
これは我校としても苦い記憶なのですが
It's a very bitter memory for our school.
さっさと車 用意しろ
Get the car ready!
ヒーローの到着は？
Have any Heroes arrived?
それがまだ
Not yet.
行くぞ イワン
Let's go, Ivan.
え？
Huh?
We're going to settle this!
俺たちで解決すんだよ
でも
外で能力使うのはダメだって校則に…
But using our powers outside is against academy rules.
そんなん関係ねえよ
That doesn't matter!
俺らの力は
人を助けるためにあるんだろ？
Our powers are meant to save people.
今使わなくて どうすんだよ？
What good are they if we don't use them?!
でも… 僕の能力じゃ
But my power is...
大丈夫 俺がサポートしてやるから
It'll be all right. I'll back you up.
行くぞ！
Let's go!
I don't think I can do this.
やっぱ… 自信ないよ
そんなんじゃ ヒーローになれねえぞ
You can't become a Hero with that attitude.
What's keeping you?! I'm really going to kill her!
まだか！　マジで殺すぞ
Give up, old man.
もう諦めな おっさん！
What the hell are you doing?
何してんだ てめぇ！
You bastard!
この野郎！
あっ 痛っ
放せよ！　くそっ！
Let me go! Damn it! Ivan!
イワン！　助けてくれよ
Help me! Hey, Ivan!
おいっ イワン！
はっ！
その件なら聞いたことがあります
I heard about that incident.
事故とは言えここから殺人者が出たって
Even if it was an accident,
one of our students was charged with murder.
その後エドワードは実刑を受け
Afterwards, Edward went to prison
ヒーローになる資格も失いました
and was no longer eligible to become a Hero.
So that's why...
だから あいつ
He should have been the Hero, not me.
彼がヒーローになるべきだったんです
その彼は今も刑務所に？
Is this friend still in prison?
それが…
Well...
ん？
久しぶりだな
Long time no see.
Edward!
エドワード
懐かしいよ
This brings back memories.
よくここでお前の相談受けたっけ
You often asked me for advice here.
どうしてここに？　だってまだ…
Why are you here? You're still...
I came for revenge.
復讐しに来たんだよ
He escaped?!
脱獄？
えぇ 数日前に連絡が…
Yes. I had a call a few days ago.
うわぁ〜っ！
Do you know how much I've suffered?
お前に俺の苦しみがわかるか
え？
Do you?!
I was so close to becoming a Hero!
俺はあと少しで
ヒーローになれたんだよ
それなのにお前が！
But because of you!
Why didn't you help me back then?
なんであの時 何もしなかった？
なんで助けに行った俺が犯罪者で
I went to save someone,
so why am I the criminal while you're the Hero?
お前がヒーローなんだよ
全部お前が悪いんだよ
It's all your fault! I lost everything because of you!
俺はお前のせいで
何もかも失ったんだ！
Origami!
折紙！
エドワード！
Edward!
チッ！
So that's him!
あいつが
Come back here!
まっ 待て この野郎！
Damn it!
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか？
なんで邪魔したんですか？
Why did you interfere?
ん？
I would die if it would make him feel better.
あいつの気が済むなら
僕は殺されても よかったんだ
何言ってんだよ
What are you saying?
だって 僕があいつの
人生を めちゃくちゃにしたから
I'm the one who ruined his life.
Edward is just looking for someone to blame.
エドワードは 逆恨みしているだけです
へっ？
Huh?
From what I can gather, you're not at fault.
話を聞く限り
折紙先輩に非はないですよ
うん
違う
No. He wanted my help back then!
あの時あいつは
僕に助けを求めてたんだ
But I...
だけど僕は…
もしあの時 僕が動いてたら
If I had moved, he could have become a Hero.
あいつはヒーローになってたのに
僕よりいいヒーローになってたのに
He would have become a better Hero than me.
This is my fault.
僕が悪いんです　僕が…
I...
だからこそ 止めてやれよ
That's why you must stop him.
へっ？
お前のせいで
あいつは罪を背負ったんだろ？
He committed a crime because of you, right?
これ以上 罪を背負わせていいのかよ
Are you going to let him commit more crimes?
でも　僕じゃ 何も…
But I can't do anything.
Are you going to repeat the same mistake?
また同じ失敗を繰り返すつもりか
あっ
Ivan!
イワン！　助けてくれよ
おい イワン！
Help me! Hey, Ivan!
Remember, you're a Hero now.
お前はもうヒーローなんだぞ
ハッ！
I sure am good.
今 いい事言ったなあ 俺
うわっ 自分で言った
You're not supposed to brag about it.
え？
Huh?
Please stop. It looks bad.
やめてくださいよ　カッコ悪い
別にいいだろう　行くぞ！
It's not a big deal! Let's go.
You have a good partner.
いいパートナーを持ったようだね
どこがですか
You're joking, right?
Edward! Edward!
エドワード！
うっ！　ぐわ〜！
What's with that face? You were looking for me, right?
なんだよ その顔
俺を探してたんだろ？
こんなこと やめようよ
Stop doing this.
Please, Edward!
ねえ！　エドワード！
うるせっ！
Shut up!
うえっ！
くっ！
はあっ！
Sinful one... Your time has come.
罪深き者よ　時は満ちた
Lunatic...
ルナティック
どうして俺を…
Why did he shoot at me?
You escaped from prison without atoning
貴様は人を殺めた罪を償わず 脱獄した
for the murder you committed.
その身を持って償うがいい
You will pay for that with your life.
はっ はぁ〜
あっ！
How foolish.
愚かな
校長はここに
Principal Massini, please stay here!
Are you all right?!
大丈夫？
ハッ！　うわぁ〜
ハッ
ウゥッ
はあ
Remember, you're a Hero now.
お前はもうヒーローなんだぞ
私から逃れられると思ったか
Did you think you could escape from me?
はぁぁっ
Wait a second.
ちょっと待ってよ
本物は僕だ
I'm the real one.
お前…
You?
You're after me, aren't you?
あんたの狙いは僕だろう　僕をやれよ
Kill me!
Senseless killing goes against my principles.
無益な殺生は主義に反する
罪人は歩み出よ
Come on out, sinner.
I told you, I'm the real one!
僕が本物だって言ってるだろ！
己の罪を償うと言うのだな
You will atone for your sins?
Very well.
よかろう
Why?!
どうして
Sinners are all cowards.
罪人は皆 卑怯だ
はぁっ
正義の裁きを受けよ
Accept the punishment of justice.
I'm going to protect Edward. I'm going to protect him!
エドワードは僕が守る
僕が守るんだ！
仕方あるまい
I guess I have no choice.
罪人をかばう者もまた悪魔だ
Those who defend sinners are also evil.
はっ！
ん？
ハァァ〜ッ！
You're not getting away!
逃がすか
よくやったぞ！　折紙
Good job, Origami!
Why are you after Edward?!
なぜエドワードを狙う
あいつはウロボロスと関係ないはずだ
He doesn't have anything to do with Ouroboros!
組織の口封じで動いてるんじゃないのか
You're not trying to silence people for your organization?
I have come to make evildoers atone for their sins.
私は悪人に罪を償わせるため舞い降りた
じゃあ お前は
ウロボロスじゃないってことか
Then you're not with Ouroboros?!
くどい
You talk too much.
Because of you, I lost my lead to Ouroboros!
お前のせいで ウロボロスの
手掛かりが途絶えたんだ
残念だったな
That's too bad.
Don't just rush in, Bunny.
無茶すんな　バニー！
ふっ！
How reckless. Has hatred consumed you?
無謀な 憎しみに我を忘れたか
Hear the voice of Thanatos.
タナトスの声を聞け
That idiot!
あっ　バカ！
あっ ぐっ
あっ
どぉ〜　ぐっ
ぐわっ
うりゃ〜
ぬぉ〜！
うぅ…
Are you all right?!
大丈夫ですか？
I'm all right... I think.
大丈夫… だと思う
くっそー
Damn it!
だから落ち着けって
I'm telling you, calm down!
しかし
But...
貴様らヒーローとの争いは
本意ではない
I have no wish to fight with you Heroes.
What?!
なに？
I am just giving murderers what they deserve.
私は人を殺めた者に
同等の償いを課してるだけだ
Is that why you kill people?
だからって 人を殺すのか？
That is my idea of justice.
それが 私の正義
Then my idea of justice is arresting idiots like you!
じゃあ 俺の正義はな…
お前みたいなバカを捕まえることだ
I shall see where your sense of justice leads you.
貴様の言う正義の行く末
しかと見届けさせてもらおう
待て！
Come back!
あいつ
That bastard.
こら 入っちゃいかん
Hey, you can't come in!
Let's start over again. My failures...
一緒にやり直そうよ
僕の失敗もエドワードの失敗も
And your failures...
うるせぇ
Shut up.
助けてくれて… ありがとな
Thanks for saving me.
え？
ずっと待ってるから
I'll be waiting for you.
Hey, Bunny.
なあ バニー
はい？
Yes?
手形野郎がウロボロスじゃないって
はっきりして良かったな
Aren't you glad that palm face wasn't related to Ouroboros?
いや… よくねえか
Guess not, huh?
Today's Hero Campaign was welcomed with
今日はヒーローキャンペーンで
各地が盛り上がりを見せましたが
a great deal of excitement from all over the city.
In particular, I'd like to credit the work of Origami Cyclone.
中でも折紙サイクロンの
活躍を評価したい
さすがはヒーローです
He is a true Hero.
From now on,
これからの拙者は
I'm not just going to stay in the background!
見切れだけでは
終わらないでござるよ シュッシュ
Shu, shu!
ふっ ははっ　痛ってぇ
Oww!
僕が消え 遠い未来で
boku ga kie tooi mirai de kaseki ni nattara
When I die and become a fossil in the far future,
化石になったら
人は僕に何を見るだろう
hito wa boku ni nani wo miru darou?
what will people see me as?
分析して 名を付けて
bunseki shite na wo tsukete kaidoku wo shitemo
They may try to analyze, name, and understand me,
解読をしても
愛した人は僕しか知らない
aishita hito wa boku shika shiranai
but only I will know the person I loved.
ハロー 生きること
HELLO ikiru koto
Hello, existence.
君の他に 君はできない
kimi no hoka ni kimi wa dekinai
Only you alone can live your life.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
僕らは何を感じられるだろう
bokura wa nani wo kanjirareru darou?
What can we feel from it?
奇跡は宇宙だけじゃないよ
kiseki wa uchuu dake janai yo
The universe isn't the only miracle.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
目を閉じたって 閉じきれないよ
me wo tojitatte tojikirenaiyo
You can try to shut your eyes, but you can't shut out your heart.
あの星さえ 持てなかった心
ano hoshi sae motenakatta kokoro
It's something that even the stars did not possess.
お前はウロボロスじゃないってことか
Then you're not with Ouroboros?!
くどい
You talk too much.
どうして僕のことなんて
Why do you bother with me?
あなたとコンビなんて
組みたくなかった
I didn't want to team up with you.
あなたに頼るつもりはありません
I have no intention of asking for your help.
僕はあなたを信じていません
I don't trust you.
ふっ
はーい！　TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
間接照明にこだわる方
バーナビーです
Hi! I'm Barnaby, the member of "Tiger & Bunny"
who's fussy about the indirect lighting in his interior design!
なんで赤ん坊なんか
預からなきゃなんないんですか
Why do we have to take care of a baby?
ちょっと
僕の部屋汚さないでください
Hey, don't mess up my room!
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
Spare the rod and spoil the child
Next time on TIGER & BUNNY:
See ya!
See you!